MAT SCALES: Hey, everyone.
MAT SCALES：大家好。
Welcome back to my Developer Diary series,
欢迎回到我的《开发人员日记》系列，
where I'm talking about how I'm making a camera app.
我在谈论如何制作相机应用。
One of the things that I want to cover in this series
我想在本系列中介绍的一件事
is places where things didn't go quite right.
是事情进展不顺利的地方。
One of the things that trips up a lot of developers,
吸引许多开发人员的一件事是，
and I wanted to experience that pain along with you,
我想和你一起经历那种痛苦
is cross-browser support.
是跨浏览器支持。
So in particular, I really need to be
所以特别地，我真的需要
able to support iOS and Android.
能够支持iOS和Android。
So that's Chrome on Android and Safari on iOS.
这就是Android上的Chrome和iOS上的Safari。
So last time, I talked about capturing images in a way that
所以上次，我谈到以一种
works across lots of browsers.
可在许多浏览器上使用。
But now, I need to be able to store them on the device.
但是现在，我需要能够将它们存储在设备上。
My initial thought was to use the CacheStorage
我最初的想法是使用CacheStorage
API, which is part of the service worker spec.
API，它是服务工作者规范的一部分。
This is a very good way of storing resources
这是一种很好的存储资源的方式
against a URL, which is perfect.
一个URL，这是完美的。
Because eventually these local resources
因为最终这些本地资源
will be uploaded to a server--
将被上传到服务器
so be able to just store them against the URL
这样就可以根据网址存储它们
they will eventually have.
他们最终将拥有。
Sadly CacheStorage is not actually implemented on Safari.
遗憾的是，实际上Safari上并未实现CacheStorage。
So instead, we have to fall back to something that is
因此，我们必须退回到某种
available on both platforms--
在两个平台上都可以使用-
IndexedDB, otherwise known as IDB.
IndexedDB，也称为IDB。
IDB isn't my favorite API, but it is very capable.
IDB不是我最喜欢的API，但功能非常强大。
So I just wrote a simple abstraction layer around it
所以我只是在它周围写了一个简单的抽象层
in order to do the things that I needed to do.
为了做我需要做的事情。
So here is that abstraction layer.
这就是抽象层。
It's a simple class that wraps around IndexedDB.
这是一个围绕IndexedDB的简单类。
And it's called an ImageDb.
它称为ImageDb。
You might notice at this point that I've actually
您可能会注意到此时我已经
written this in TypeScript.
用TypeScript编写。
If you're not familiar with TypeScript,
如果您不熟悉TypeScript，
just take any of these parts that's
只是把这些部分
like a colon and then a type, and just pretend
像冒号然后是类型，然后假装
it's documentation.
它是文档。
TypeScript is really just JavaScript
TypeScript实际上只是JavaScript
with this little extra layer on top.
上面有这个额外的小层。
That said, let's talk about what this is actually doing.
就是说，让我们讨论一下这实际上是在做什么。
So when you create an ImageDB, it creates the database
因此，当您创建ImageDB时，它将创建数据库
and sets up these event handlers.
并设置这些事件处理程序。
Nothing particularly exciting there.
那里没有什么特别令人兴奋的。
I've got a method for storing this thing, which
我有一种方法来存储这个东西，
is called an ImageRecord.
称为ImageRecord。
An ImageRecord is just--
ImageRecord只是-
it's a plain object that stores the images and any metadata
这是一个普通的对象，用于存储图像和任何元数据
that I need about those images.
我需要这些图像。
Then I can retrieve an ImageRecord from the database.
然后，我可以从数据库中检索ImageRecord。
I've got a method here called all,
我这里有一个叫做全部的方法，
which just gets all of the image records
仅获取所有图像记录
that are in the database.
在数据库中。
This is used for the browse page,
这用于浏览页面，
where I show all of the images that are available.
在这里显示所有可用的图像。
And then there's these sort of internal helpers here.
然后这里有这些内部帮手。
And the only real important one here
而这里唯一真正重要的
is the createObjectStore method, which actually creates
是createObjectStore方法，实际上是
the database the first time you go to the app, or grades
您第一次访问该应用程序或成绩时的数据库
it if you've been there before with an older
如果您以前和大人一起去过
version of the application.
应用程序的版本。
So this layer was working pretty great for me,
所以这一层对我来说非常有效，
but I soon ran into a problem.
但我很快遇到了问题。
So the ImageRecord objects that I'm using,
因此，我正在使用的ImageRecord对象，
I was originally using blobs to store any image data.
我最初使用blob来存储任何图像数据。
I mean, this made perfect sense.
我的意思是，这很合理。
When I wanted to get an image through file upload, copy
当我想通过文件上传获取图像时，请复制
and paste, getting an image out of a canvas,
粘贴，从画布上获取图像，
they all gave me a blob.
他们都给了我一个斑点。
And when I wanted to display an image, I'd get a blob
当我想显示图像时，会出现斑点
and get its URL and use that blob URL
并获取其URL并使用该Blob URL
as the source of an image.
作为图像的来源。
Unfortunately, you can't store blobs in Safari on iOS at all.
不幸的是，您根本无法在iOS的Safari中存储Blob。
What you can do is store an ArrayBuffer.
您可以做的就是存储一个ArrayBuffer。
So instead of using blobs everywhere,
因此，与其在各处使用Blob，
I just need to do a little bit of conversion
我只需要做一点转换
any time that I get a blob, turn it
每当我出现斑点时，都将其转动
into an ArrayBuffer to store it, and turn it back
放入ArrayBuffer进行存储，然后将其转回
into a blob to use it.
变成斑点来使用它。
So let's have a look at that conversion.
因此，让我们看一下该转换。
So if you have an ArrayBuffer and you
因此，如果您有ArrayBuffer并且
want to turn it into a blob, that's pretty easy.
想把它变成斑点，这很容易。
You use the blob constructor.
您使用Blob构造函数。
You pass in the ArrayBuffer in an array as the first element.
您将数组中的ArrayBuffer作为第一个元素传入。
And then you just pass in the type that you want it to be.
然后，您只需传递您想要的类型即可。
So here, this will be something like image/jpeg.
所以在这里，这将类似于image / jpeg。
To go the other way around is slightly more complicated.
相反，稍微复杂一点。
So I created a little helper here.
所以我在这里创建了一个小助手。
If you want to take a blob and turn it into an ArrayBuffer,
如果您想将Blob转换为ArrayBuffer，
you can use the FileReader API.
您可以使用FileReader API。
So you create a FileReader.
因此，您创建了FileReader。
And then you say that you want to readAsArrayBuffer some blob.
然后，您说您想要readAsArrayBuffer一些Blob。
And then, eventually, you get this Loadend event.
然后，最终，您得到此Loadend事件。
And here, you can see, I've wrapped in a Promise.
在这里，您可以看到，我包裹在一个Promise中。
And I just resolve with the result.
我只是解决结果。
So there you go.
所以你去了。
It was kind of tricky to work out how to get around this.
弄清楚如何解决这个问题有点棘手。
But in the end, it was possible.
但最终，这是可能的。
Sure, you can't store blobs in IDB on iOS,
当然，您无法在iOS的IDB中存储Blob，
but there was a way around it.
但是有办法解决。
And that's the story for a lot of web development nowadays.
这就是当今许多Web开发的故事。
Modern web development is all about finding out what
现代Web开发就是要找出什么
works across all the browsers.
适用于所有浏览器。
Hopefully, this is getting easier over time.
希望随着时间的推移，这会变得越来越容易。
But you know, these things will still happen.
但您知道，这些事情仍然会发生。
So hopefully that was useful to anyone who's
因此希望这对那些
coming across the same problem.
遇到同样的问题。
And join me next time when we'll learn about something new.
下次加入我们的行列时，我们将学习新的知识。
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
Thanks for watching.
感谢收看。
If you'd like to see more of our videos,
如果您想观看我们更多的视频，
click here, and see you again.
单击此处，然后再见。
Cheers.
干杯。